25/2/2021 LeKhaTiep Resume



Lê Khả Tiệp

ASP.NET Developer

About Me

I have 1 year of experience in working as web developer .Experience with OOP, SOLID principles, Design Patterns .Create and execute Unit Test and Integration Test

Age 26

Email tieplekha@gmail.com

Phone 0909-761-609

Address 41/10 Mai Lao Bang, Ward

13,Tan Binh District, Ho Chi

Minh City

Technical Skills

 Programming skills: C# ASP.Net, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

https://lekhatiep.github.io/cv.html

- · Database: SQL Server
- · Tool: Visual Studio 2019 GitKraken, Redmine, Jira

Personality

- · Hardworking, careful, friendly communicate
- · Quick learning and time management
- Problem-solving skill
- Good ability to learn new technology following requirement

Work Experience

Freelancer Developer

09.2020 - 01.2021

Website money transfer

The system transfer money between national. The administrator manages agent, report, transaction and

https://lekhatiep.github.io/cv.html

request from the affiliate. The agent can create a transaction for beneficiaries etc...

Duties

- · Develop front-end and back-end
- Implement new features following requirement
- Support other team members
- · Taking care of maintenance and enhancement

Technologies

- Database: SQL Server
- Programming Language: C#
- Library: Jquery
- Framework: ASP.NET MVC
- Source control: GIT

Backend Developer at RikkeiSoft

09.2020 - 01.2021

Patient Management Mobile App

This app using for Hospital and Patient hemophilia. The patient must install the app after visit the hospital. The app saves data info related to the reason for hemorrhage. Remind to use the medicine every day

Duties

- Create Unit Test in Excel File
- Develop back-end API
- Implement new features following requirement
- Support other team members

25/2/2021 LeKhaTiep Resume

• Taking care of maintenance and enhancement

Technologies

• Database: SQL Server

• Programming Language: C#

• Library: Jquery

• Framework: ASP.NET Core API

• Source control: GIT

https://lekhatiep.github.io/cv.html 4/6

Education

Degree of Associate Information Technology from Tran Dai Nghia University

2013 - 2016

Contact

Address

41/10, Mai Lao Bang, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City, VN

Phone

+84-909-761-609

Email

tieplekha@gmail.com

- https://github.com/lekhatiep
- https://www.hackerrank.com/tieplk
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/lekhatiep/